justclicktowatch.to 2014-12-21

# Privacy Policy ⋆ Watch movies online free

#### Information Collection:

When you visit Justclicktowatch.so, we will not collect any personally identifiable information about you unless you choose to provide such information to us.

#### Log Files:

We may automatically and through third-party tracking services (e.g., Google Analytics) gather certain non-personally identifiable information about your use of Justclicktowatch and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamps, and related data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, solely to improve the quality of our services. Out of respect for your privacy, we do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

#### Cookies:

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use both session ID cookies and tracking cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to use Justclicktowatch. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. We use tracking cookies to better understand how you use Justclicktowatch, and to enhance your user experience. A tracking cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You are free to decline cookies, but by doing so, you may not be able to take full advantage of all of our offerings. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while using Justclicktowatch.

#### Email Privacy:

A free subscription to any of JCTW’s newsletters come with her 100 Percent Spam-Free Guarantee. JCTW’s newsletters are also “Can-Spam” compliant.We will never sell your email address to any third parties, ever. If we ever sell your email address to anybody, we agree that you can beat us with a large metal object. The object must be at least 4 feet long and weigh more than 20lbs.

#### Links to Other Websites:

Our Services may be accessed through, or provide you with access to, other websites and services. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such websites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of each and every such website. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected through the Services.

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy:

From time to time, Justclicktowatch will review and may edit this policy in accordance with potential changes to our business and as required by law. Justclicktowatch reserves the right to change its Privacy Policy at any time.

#### More Privacy Stuff:

Our advertisers require us to add this paragraph as well.

“We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org.”
